<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01300 75W90 Max Gear Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01300 75W90 Max Gear OilMax-Gear is an ultra-tough automotive gear oil. It’s designed to maximize power and provide unsurpassed protection to heavily loaded gears. It makes gears run smoother, quieter, cooler and longer without overhauls.Max-Gear outperforms other gear oils because it combines the highest quality synthetic oils with Royal Purple’s proprietary Synslide additive technology.Max-Gear is recommended for use in truck, motor home  RV, and automotive front or rear differentials, manual transmissions, and lower gear units of marine engines that specify use of an API GL-5 or GL-4 fluid. All viscosities of Max-Gear are formulated with hypoid friction modifiers necessary for use in clutch or cone type differentials. No additional additives are necessary.</description>
<g:id>ROY1300</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/maxgear-02.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181272</link>
<g:price>16.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 05303 85W140 Max-Gear Oil-5 Gallon Pail</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 05303 85W140 Max-Gear Oil-5 Gallon PailMax-Gear is an ultra-tough automotive gear oil. It’s designed to maximize power and provide unsurpassed protection to heavily loaded gears. It makes gears run smoother, quieter, cooler and longer without overhauls.Max-Gear outperforms other gear oils because it combines the highest quality synthetic oils with Royal Purple’s proprietary Synslide additive technology.Max-Gear is recommended for use in truck, motor home  RV, and automotive front or rear differentials, manual transmissions, and lower gear units of marine engines that specify use of an API GL-5 or GL-4 fluid. All viscosities of Max-Gear are formulated with hypoid friction modifiers necessary for use in clutch or cone type differentials. No additional additives are necessary.</description>
<g:id>ROY5303</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/5g-02.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181271</link>
<g:price>265.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 10036 Synthetic Gun Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 10036 Synthetic Gun OilRoyal Purple’s Synthetic Gun Oil is specifically formulated to provide exceptional protection against wear, rust and saltwater corrosion and fouling. It works well in a variety of temperatures and will not thicken in cold weather.Its performance advantages come from Synerlec, Royal Purple’s proprietary chemical technology that strengthens the oil for unmatched performance and protection.World Champion Sporting Clay Shooter and Elite Shooting School Instructor Bobby Fowler, Jr. said, “I’ve tried every gun lube out there. None of them compare to Royal Purple.”</description>
<g:id>ROY10036</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/10036.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181262</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01512 Synchromax Gear Lube</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01512 Synchromax Gear LubeSynchromax is a manual transmission fluid that increases performance and the life of your equipment. It improves shifting, reduces gear noise and increases power transfer to the wheels. It also lowers operating temperatures and provides outstanding wear protection for longer transmission life.Synchromax is recommended for manual transmissions that specify an automatic transmission fluid. It’s also ideal for 4? transfer cases and motorcycle gear boxes. Synchromax is fully compatible with all types of friction materials. It provides excellent corrosion and oxidation protection without affecting the soft metals commonly found in manual transmission synchronizers.Synchromax is formulated with Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology for unsurpassed performance and protection.</description>
<g:id>ROY1512</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/01512.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181260</link>
<g:price>12.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01540 5W40 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01540 5W40 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1540</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-13.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181261</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 04154 15W40 Motor Oil-Gallon Jug</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 04154 15W40 Motor Oil-Gallon JugRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY4154</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/04154.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181259</link>
<g:price>29.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01303 85W140 Max-Gear Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01303 85W140 Max-Gear OilMax-Gear is an ultra-tough automotive gear oil. It’s designed to maximize power and provide unsurpassed protection to heavily loaded gears. It makes gears run smoother, quieter, cooler and longer without overhauls.Max-Gear outperforms other gear oils because it combines the highest quality synthetic oils with Royal Purple’s proprietary Synslide additive technology.Max-Gear is recommended for use in truck, motor home  RV, and automotive front or rear differentials, manual transmissions, and lower gear units of marine engines that specify use of an API GL-5 or GL-4 fluid. All viscosities of Max-Gear are formulated with hypoid friction modifiers necessary for use in clutch or cone type differentials. No additional additives are necessary.</description>
<g:id>ROY1303</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/maxgear.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181257</link>
<g:price>16.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 11487 Break-In Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 11487 Break-In Motor OilEngine builders have grown increasingly concerned that many modern motor oils do not provide adequate wear protection for new engines, particularly those using flat-tappet cams. Royal Purple has addressed this issue by developing a new engine break-in oil.Royal Purple Break-in Oil is formulated to allow optimal ring seal and protect rotating assembly components such as the camshaft and valve train from initial start up wear. Royal Purple combines highly refined mineral oil, preferred for engine break-in, with advanced additives containing high levels of zinc and phosphorus to optimize protection in flat-tappet and roller engines.Royal Purple Break-in Oil is fully formulated and does not require the use of any other chemical additives. Royal Purple recommends using their high performance motor oils after the engine is broken in for maximum engine performance.</description>
<g:id>ROY11487</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/11487.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181258</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01335 Max-Tuff Assembly Lube</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01335 Max-Tuff Assembly LubeMax-Tuff is an ultra-tough, synthetic lubricant designed for use in reassembling repaired equipment.Max-Tuff utilizes durable synthetic molecules that adhere to metal surfaces and create an extremely strong barrier between surfaces. This minimizes the possibility of metal-to-metal contact while providing excellent protection against rust and corrosion to both ferrous and nonferrous metals.Max-Tuff is formulated with Royal Purple’s proprietary Synslide additive technology.</description>
<g:id>ROY1335</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/01335.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181264</link>
<g:price>15.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01040 SAE 40 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01040 SAE 40 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1040</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-15.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181265</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01030 SAE 30 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01030 SAE 30 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1030</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-17.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181268</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 11484 0W40 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 11484 0W40 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY11484</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-14.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181263</link>
<g:price>10.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 05950 Nitro Plus 50 Motor Oil-5 Gallon Pail</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 05950 Nitro Plus 50 Motor Oil-5 Gallon PailRoyal Purple’s Nitro Plus Racing Oils are straight-grade, non-foaming, synthetic engine oils formulated specifically for use in blown alcohol or nitromethane applications.“Running Royal Purple in my engines over the years has been a key component to helping me gain the competitive edge over my competition as well as my repeated trips to the winners circle,” says Clay Millican, 5-time IHRA Top Fuel Champion. “Not worrying about my oil getting mixed up with my fuel leaves me able to focus on more important things at the track, like winning. I would recommend any of Royal Purple’s products to other racers out there.”</description>
<g:id>ROY5950</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/5g-01.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181270</link>
<g:price>316.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01050 SAE 50 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01050 SAE 50 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1050</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-16.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181266</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01301 75W140 Max-Gear Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01301 75W140 Max-Gear OilMax-Gear is an ultra-tough automotive gear oil. It’s designed to maximize power and provide unsurpassed protection to heavily loaded gears. It makes gears run smoother, quieter, cooler and longer without overhauls.Max-Gear outperforms other gear oils because it combines the highest quality synthetic oils with Royal Purple’s proprietary Synslide additive technology.Max-Gear is recommended for use in truck, motor home  RV, and automotive front or rear differentials, manual transmissions, and lower gear units of marine engines that specify use of an API GL-5 or GL-4 fluid. All viscosities of Max-Gear are formulated with hypoid friction modifiers necessary for use in clutch or cone type differentials. No additional additives are necessary.</description>
<g:id>ROY1301</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/maxgear-01.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181267</link>
<g:price>16.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 05040 SAE 40 Motor Oil-5 Gallon Pail</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 05040 SAE 40 Motor Oil-5 Gallon PailRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY5040</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/5g.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181269</link>
<g:price>145.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01250 20W50 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01250 20W50 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1250</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181241</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01051 20W50 XPR Racing Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01051 20W50 XPR Racing Motor OilXPR — Extreme Performance Racing oils are formulated for demanding applications such as racing, modified engines and off-road use. XPR’s high film strength make it exceptionally well-suited for today’s high performance cars and trucks, particularly turbo and supercharged engines and  or engines using a nitrous boost.XPR produces winning results on the race track and is safe enough to use in your daily commuter car.Professional engine builders and race teams cite increased horsepower and torque, and longer engine life with the use of Royal Purple. Be sure to follow the manufacturer's and  or engine builder's recommendations when selecting an oil viscosity.</description>
<g:id>ROY1051</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-01.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181242</link>
<g:price>14.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01530 5W30 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01530 5W30 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1530</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-02.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181243</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01320 Max ATF Transmission Fluid</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01320 Max ATF Transmission FluidMax ATF is a synthetic, high-performance, automatic transmission fluid. Its low co-efficient of friction and high film strength help to dramatically reduce heat and wear. Additionally, Max ATF is more oxidation stable than other transmission fluids for longer fluid life.Max ATF is recommended for a wide variety of transmissions. See our transmission lubricant cross reference chart for specific applications.Max ATF significantly reduces heat to extend the life of your transmission. Automatic transmissions generate a great deal of heat and depend upon the transmission fluid for cooling and protection. More than 90 percent of all automatic transmission failures are caused by overheating; a 20 degreesF reduction in fluid temperature can double the life of the transmission (Source: Perma Industries, Inc.).Max ATF is fully compatible and can be mixed with other automatic transmission fluids; however, for the best results drain or flush the current oil and then fill with Max ATF.</description>
<g:id>ROY1320</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/01320.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181244</link>
<g:price>11.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01600 Purple Ice Coolant Additive</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01600 Purple Ice Coolant AdditivePurple Ice is a high performance, synthetic, radiator coolant additive. It reduces engine heat by reducing the surface tension of the radiator fluids for improved heat transfer.Purple Ice fosters optimum coolant flow by helping to prevent formation of scale deposits in the radiator. It also lubricates the water pump seals.Purple Ice should always be used in conjunction with antifreeze in regions where freezing temperatures occur. Purple Ice is compatible with traditional ethylene glycol antifreeze (green) and GM Dex-Cool® antifreeze.</description>
<g:id>ROY1600</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/01600.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181245</link>
<g:price>14.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01520 5W20 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01520 5W20 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1520</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-03.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181246</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01130 10W30 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01130 10W30 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1130</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-04.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181247</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01316 20W50 Max-Cycle ATV & Motorcycle Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01316 20W50 Max-Cycle ATV  Motorcycle OilMax-Cycle is specifically formulated to significantly improve motorcycle, ATV and snowmobile engine (and transmission) performance. It’s recommended for use in both air-cooled and liquid-cooled 4-cycle engines and it’s compatible with wet-clutch transmissions.</description>
<g:id>ROY1316</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-05.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181248</link>
<g:price>13.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01154 15W40 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01154 15W40 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1154</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-06.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181249</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01011 5W20 XPR Racing Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01011 5W20 XPR Racing Motor OilXPR — Extreme Performance Racing oils are formulated for demanding applications such as racing, modified engines and off-road use. XPR’s high film strength make it exceptionally well-suited for today’s high performance cars and trucks, particularly turbo and supercharged engines and  or engines using a nitrous boost.XPR produces winning results on the race track and is safe enough to use in your daily commuter car.Professional engine builders and race teams cite increased horsepower and torque, and longer engine life with the use of Royal Purple. Be sure to follow the manufacturer's and  or engine builder's recommendations when selecting an oil viscosity.</description>
<g:id>ROY1011</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-07.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181250</link>
<g:price>14.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01041 10W40 XPR Racing Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01041 10W40 XPR Racing Motor OilXPR — Extreme Performance Racing oils are formulated for demanding applications such as racing, modified engines and off-road use. XPR’s high film strength make it exceptionally well-suited for today’s high performance cars and trucks, particularly turbo and supercharged engines and  or engines using a nitrous boost.XPR produces winning results on the race track and is safe enough to use in your daily commuter car.Professional engine builders and race teams cite increased horsepower and torque, and longer engine life with the use of Royal Purple. Be sure to follow the manufacturer's and  or engine builder's recommendations when selecting an oil viscosity.</description>
<g:id>ROY1041</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-08.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181251</link>
<g:price>14.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01326 Max EZ Power Steering Fluid</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01326 Max EZ Power Steering FluidMax EZ is an advanced power steering fluid designed to maximize the life and performance of all power steering units.Max EZ is formulated with a blend of select synthetic base oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary  Synerlec additive technology, which is proven to make equipment run cooler, smoother, longer, quieter and more efficiently. Max EZ is compatible and can be mixed with conventional power steering fluids and has excellent seal compatibility.</description>
<g:id>ROY1326</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/01326.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181252</link>
<g:price>4.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01021 5W30 XPR Racing Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01021 5W30 XPR Racing Motor OilXPR — Extreme Performance Racing oils are formulated for demanding applications such as racing, modified engines and off-road use. XPR’s high film strength make it exceptionally well-suited for today’s high performance cars and trucks, particularly turbo and supercharged engines and  or engines using a nitrous boost.XPR produces winning results on the race track and is safe enough to use in your daily commuter car.Professional engine builders and race teams cite increased horsepower and torque, and longer engine life with the use of Royal Purple. Be sure to follow the manufacturer's and  or engine builder's recommendations when selecting an oil viscosity.</description>
<g:id>ROY1021</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-09.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181253</link>
<g:price>14.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01315 10W40 Max-Cycle ATV & Motorcycle Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01315 10W40 Max-Cycle ATV  Motorcycle OilMax-Cycle is specifically formulated to significantly improve motorcycle, ATV and snowmobile engine (and transmission) performance. It’s recommended for use in both air-cooled and liquid-cooled 4-cycle engines and it’s compatible with wet-clutch transmissions.</description>
<g:id>ROY1315</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-10.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181254</link>
<g:price>13.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01009 0W10 XPR Racing Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01009 0W10 XPR Racing Motor OilXPR — Extreme Performance Racing oils are formulated for demanding applications such as racing, modified engines and off-road use. XPR’s high film strength make it exceptionally well-suited for today’s high performance cars and trucks, particularly turbo and supercharged engines and  or engines using a nitrous boost.XPR produces winning results on the race track and is safe enough to use in your daily commuter car.Professional engine builders and race teams cite increased horsepower and torque, and longer engine life with the use of Royal Purple. Be sure to follow the manufacturer's and  or engine builder's recommendations when selecting an oil viscosity.</description>
<g:id>ROY1009</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-11.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181255</link>
<g:price>14.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
<item>
<title>Royal Purple 01140 10W40 Motor Oil</title>
<g:brand>Royal Purple Synthetic Oil</g:brand>
<g:condition>new</g:condition>
<description>Royal Purple 01140 10W40 Motor OilRoyal Purple Motor Oil delivers superior protection and improves performance in four-cycle gasoline and diesel engines. It increases horsepower and torque, saves fuels and reduces heat, wear and emissions. It has unsurpassed oxidation stability that allows for extended oil drains and fewer oil changes, which saves you time and money and reduces the impact on the environment.Royal Purple’s performance advantages come from a blend of synthetic oils plus Royal Purple’s proprietary Synerlec technology. Royal Purple Motor Oil is compatible with other mineral and synthetic motor oils.</description>
<g:id>ROY1140</g:id>
<g:image_link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/images/P/oil-12.jpg</g:image_link>
<link>http://www.tennesseespeedsport.com/product.php?productid=181256</link>
<g:price>7.99</g:price>
<g:type>Performance Auto Parts</g:type>
</item>
